When the clock strikes one o'clock,
the skeletons come out of their graves
Bibbidi-bobbidi-boo
When the clock strikes two o'clock,
the skeletons come eat their gruel
Bibbidi-bobbidi-boo
When the clock strikes three o'clock,
the skeletons skip on one foot
Bibbidi-bobbidi-boo
When the clock strikes four o'clock,
the skeletons go to the theater
What do you see?
A pine...
It's called nopal.
Nopal,
the beach,
a hotel.
What else?
A road,
a castle
and sand.
What about you, Max?
What do you see?
Nothing.
Are we near Disney now?
The Wolves
Mr. Chang?
Apartment?
Mom, I'm thirsty.
For rent!
2 bedroom apartment
It's all chill around here,
you know what I mean?
As for the bathroom,
you gotta share it with other people.
About the rent,
rent is 600 if you want it.
We have a one bedroom
apartment for you to rent.
We have half this place,
everything working,
for 400 dollars a month.
-Hey!
The woman with the two kids are back
asking about the unit.
Hurry, take care of them!
- Why did you quote
such low rent to her?
Of course she's back!
-$500 is good enough!
-Ugh! Here we go again,
I always have to take care of things
that you messed up.
Let's go.
Go ahead, Max.
Good?
300.
Max, put that down.
One more.
Thank you.
No, no, no.
You don't know where it's been.
Leo, get down from there.
Let's go.
Max, let's go.
Yours.
Mine.
Give it to me!
Don't you start!
Where are we sleeping?
On the floor, you dumbass.
We'll make a bed
out of blankets.
It's the same thing.
Want to hear grandpa instead?
Wait, I'm coming!
Leo.
Max.
- What is it?
- I'll be going now.
- Where to?
- Work.
- We'll come with you.
- You can't.
- We'll get dressed and come with you.
- You can't, we've gone over this.
I need to work so we can
have money and live...
To go to Disney?
- Yes, to go to Disney.
- Disney, Disney!
- Shut up!
- Hey, stop it!
We need some rules.
Rule number one:
never leave the apartment.
What if there's a fire?
If there's a fire, you may leave.
Rule number 2:
don't step on the carpet without shoes.
Rule number 3:
keep the apartment
clean and tidy.
Rule number 4:
look after your brother.
Rule number 5:
make up with a hug
after a fight.
No giving the finger.
Are you giving the finger?
Are you hugging him?
How are you hugging him?
Rule number 6:
don't cry.
Rule number 7:
don't lie.
Leo, what's rule number 2?
What if there's a fire?
If there's a fire, you may leave.
Rule number 2:
don't step on the carpet without shoes.
Don't step on the carpet
without shoes.
I'm giving you the recorder
so you can learn the rules by heart.
If you want to add any rules
we can record them as well.
I'll be back by the time
the clock strikes seven o'clock.
Bibbidi-bobbidi-boo.
Max.
You're in charge.
Max!
You hear that?
I did.
Kiss me goodbye, now.
- What are we?
- Wolves.
Run.
Stop.
Your butt'll fall off.
Goal!
Wait!
Can you tie them for me?
You should learn
to tie them yourself.
For Christ's sake.
Lazy bum.
Wait, I'm...
Did you play?
We ran a lot
and played some soccer.
What's that?
A card to work.
You need a card to work?
You do here.
Effortless English
You take the both of them,
put them together,
wrap this one around, pull it,
then you make
a couple of bunny ears,
like this,
you put them together,
you wrap it around and pull.
You do it now.
No, dummy.
You pull, put them together,
wrap one around and pull again,
make the bunny ears,
wrap one around and do it like this.
You do it again now.
No giving the finger.
Are you giving the finger?
Are you hugging him?
How are you hugging him?
Brother.
Want to play ninja wolves?
I can smash everything with my fists.
What about me?
You're lightning fast and...
you can stretch.
I can stretch, but
can't I smash things?
You can't smash things.
You can only stretch
and have lightning speed.
5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
5, 6, 7...
8, 9, 10.
You're such a shorty!
Tlajomulco Police Department
I can't remember him anymore.
What about you?
No.
I heard mom told the neighbor
dad went away by light bulb.
By the light bulb! How?
Don't know.
I asked mom, she got angry
and stayed mum.
Stop crying, sissy.
What happened, Leo?
You said you'd be here by 7.
I didn't make it.
I'm here now.
Leo, what's that?
Max, what's that?
What's rule number 3?
Keep what?
Keep the apartment
clean and tidy.
So what's this?
It's not dirty.
Don't you try and be smart now, Max.
Here.
Scribble on these instead.
Leo, take it.
Look what I brought.
Want some?
Boys!
- Boys!
The one in red!
- Boys.
- The one in blue!
- Bunch of dumbasses!
Dumbasses!
What do you want fucker?
Come!
Don't be cowards!
Give me the ball!
Give it to me.
You said we were going to Disney.
We agreed I have
to save up first, remember?
So when are we going?
I'm giving you a challenge.
Once you master it,
we'll go to Disney.
The challenge is
to learn the whole alphabet in English,
numbers 1 to 20
and lessons 1 and 2.
You also need to learn
how to ask for a ticket,
or else they won't
understand you when we go.
You need to learn how to say,
"may I have a ticket, please?"
How do you say that?
Hand me the recorder and
I'll record it for you right away.
Your turn now.
I can't.
What do you mean you can't?
- How so?
- My mom'll scold me.
- Doesn't matter, just come.
- Ours scold us too.
We can tell you're bored
in there, just come.
I have to look after my little brother.
- Stay there then, pussy!
- Your loss.
Mom.
What is it?
When are we going to school?
Soon, I just need to
take care of some things first.
Mom.
Go to sleep now.
Why am I so short?
Because you take after me.
So Leo takes after dad?
Neither of you take after your father.
You both take after me.
Go to sleep now.
Mom.
Mom!
You are strong wolves!
Wolves don't cry.
Wolves bite.
They howl.
And they protect their home.
How do wolves howl?
We better use the light bulb
or they'll kill us all!
Let's run away by light bulb!
I'm gonna throw you fire!
At what time are you coming back?
Late, the other job is further away!
Why don't we just go back home?
Good.
What is this?
A present from the chinese lady.
Tastes like crumb.
Tlajomulco Police Deparment.
Where? Here?
I got a cut.
Well, I didn't.
The thing is,
your grandpa was sick
and he kept forgetting everything.
And I do mean everything,
his name, his address, where he was.
He even forgot I was his daughter.
Then one day, I entered his room
to watch some ships in a bottle he had.
He was fond of collecting those.
So when he walked in
he started screaming, calling me
a thief and telling me to stay put.
I found that funny and
broke out in laughter.
He got so mad at my laughter,
so he took one of his bottles
and smashed it over my head,
then I ducked for cover
and when the glass shards fell
and made some noise
I saw some blood.
I thought he might have
cut himself, so I checked him up
but he didn't have any wounds.
That's when I realized
I was the one who got a cut,
when I checked I could even
see the muscle covered in blood.
Mom.
- Mom!
We already memorized the lessons.
We already know how
to ask for a ticket in English.
-Stop!
Disney is 12 hours away from here,
You get that or not?
It's really far!
I won't take you now, Max!
But you promised.
I never said I'd take you
right away, Max.
I never said that!
It's Sunday.
I have to go to work later.
Don't you get that?
Let me sleep, please!
Liar.
What'd you call me?
It's your fault dad
went away by light bulb.
I can't.
Do it now, mom won't open up.
Rule number 7
I'm Max, I'm Max!
I'm going out.
Look after the place.
Mom will scold us.
- Mom doesn't follow the rules.
- Max!
They let you come out?
Can I play?
Grandpa.
You beat everyone.
What are you doing here?
A monster was eating a lady.
Shut up, come!
When mom comes back
you'll take the blame for this.
No, you went outside first.
We're stuck outside.
Let's go.
What is that?
They want me to do occupational therapy.
It’s supposed to be good for my health.
You have to understand where we come from
and know where we are.
This is me.
That is my son,
but he became a gang member.
He’s gone now!
Gangs are no good!
Cholo (Thug).
Cholo?
No?
Cholo no good!
No cholo in my house.
No gangs here.
Haven’t taken your pills, right?
The more pills I take,
the more I feel sick!
But it’s time to take your pills.
I’m not leaving until you take them!
Take it or not, will die anyway!
Whatever!
Eat.
Say it!
Repeat.
Eat.
Ok! Let’s go eat!
Forget him!
Mom.
What is it?
Did you have nightmares?
So?
I killed Grandpa.
Grandpa.
I want to introduce you
to some friends.
Give it back!
- He doesn't know English!
- He doesn't?
I do.
What do you know?
We'll be at the park
if you want to hang out.
Don't tell mom.
Mom!
Mom.
Max, Leo!
Max!
Leo, wake up!
Where's the potato chip can?
The can with all of our savings!
It was there yesterday
and now it's gone!
Where is it?
Answer me!
The potato chip can turn up in one,
the potato chip can turn up in two,
- The potato chip can turn up...
- It was Max's friends!
- What?
- Max's friends.
What friends?
- Where does he live?
- Over there.
Speak Spanish?
Your son took a potato chip can
with all of our savings.
My son?
Your son Kevin.
Kevin?
How do you know it was him?
Answer!
Leo saw him.
I didn't.
Give it back!
Hurry and get dressed now!
I'm taking you with me.
Brother.
Want to play ninja wolves?
Why did you eat the last one?
You ate more of them.
Soup kitchen, homeless shelter
and rehab center
Soup kitchen
- So everyone...
- so everyone...
- who has faith in him...
- may live...
- forever.
- Forever.
Today we'll learn
about a missionary,
this is based on a true story
from Nicaragua.
With the country at war,
some missionaries were in danger.
The people of Jalapa
were trapped in a war zone.
At the same time,
a bigger battle was raging.
It was a spiritual battle.
Although distant gunshots
could be heard,
the people gathered in the middle
of the night to worship God.
The people gathered in the middle
He received a terrible message.
A group of men was planning
to kill him that very night.
No one was aware that a young man
had entered the service carrying a gun.
His objective was
to kill the missionary.
But when he looked up at the altar
he saw an amazing sight.
The missionary was surrounded
by angels shining brightly.
Terrified, the young man fled.
Satan fought hard to reign over Jalapa,
but God's power was greater.
Would any of you like to do
missionary work somewhere?
- Azael.
- Russia.
Russia
- Sophie.
- To Colorado.
To Colorado. Why?
Because I miss my friend there.
You could be with your friend
and talk to her about Jesus.
- Hollywood.
- That's great, why there?
There is a great evil there.
My mom said there were many
naked ladies trying to sell their body.
- Ariel.
- Mexico.
- Why there, Ariel?
- So I can get my papers fixed.
- Yes.
- To Disney.
Disney?
Why Disney?
Because there's many attractions.
Let me tell you something.
In God's hands,
life changes.
Amen!
- Life changes.
- Amen!
Jesus has the power
to change history.
God believes in you.
Your sin, my sin,
my lacking, my failure,
God is not disappointed in you
and God loves you all the same.
God loves you all the same.
Close your eyes, let's pray!
Wondrous God, we thank you once more
I thank you on behalf of every life
gathered here on this Sunday afternoon.
I beg you to enter their lives
to touch their hearts
and heal their wounds
and restore them, my Lord
By the mighty name of God,
take my life
Take my life!
We give ourselves unto you and toss
aside anything that might interfere.
-Thank you!
- Welcome, good afternoon!
- Good afternoon!
-Hello
-It's nice to see you!
Leo, take one of those...
and some bread.
- Good afternoon.
-Welcome! God bless you.
- Welcome!
- I’ve had enough of you!
Why don’t you just talk to yourself!
Leave me alone!
No, here. Like this.
You terrible boys!
Wait till I catch!
Come.
Just a little while?
But first, clean.
Oh! Repeat, ok?
Got some!
Thanks!
- Ok! Thank you.
- You're welcome.
One time I had diarrhea.
I pooped.
- All day long.
- What color?
Green, red and yellow.
Blue, purple.
Those colors.
How about you?
What...
What's your favorite soccer team?
Chivas and Mexico's national team.
And yours?
Wait, I'm coming!
Max, you're awake.
What's your costume?
Ninjas.
There's one for you too.
That's not just for girls!
-Girls' songs!
What do you mean there are
boys' songs and girls' songs?
Leo.
-Max...
my home.
Would you like for the Changs
to look after you in the afternoons?
I know it's not Disney.
What do you see?
A pine...
It's called nopal.
Nopal,
the beach,
a hotel.
What else?
A road,
a castle,
and sand.
What about you, Max?
What do you see?
-Wait, I'm coming!